Hello everyone. I am Director Hoshi of Uguka no Mura. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, thank you all for your many questions. I will answer them now.
What made me happy recently is that I got to cut my own bangs.
I have three friends who became good friends with me when we were in the second year of junior high school,
We don't see each other very often, and when we do see each other, it is every two years or so,
I would like to go on a hot spring trip with them.
Q. Where do you see monowadaka?
Where do you think?
Where do you see monowadaka?
I would like to go to the Maldives, a place with beautiful scenery.
I often say, "I'm sure, I've heard that before, but I've heard it a lot. I often say, "I'm not sure.
Q. Who likes anime and games?
I'm interested in Sakura Seta, who will be with me at Tokyo Yakan Land vol.3. I heard that she likes anime and games, so I'd like to talk to her.
Q. What makes me feel like I've become an adult is that I can now eat spicy food,
I used to think that even slightly spicy food was too much for me, but now I can eat spicy food again. I used to be like, "Oh, I can't!
But now I can eat spicy food such as Bean-curd soup with hot sauce and enjoy it. I can now eat spicy food like bean-curd soup and other spicy food with a big smattering of flavor,
I thought I had grown up.
I don't even remember Nail Masters anymore.
A friend of mine recommended it to me.
I was doing it with them for a while.
I was playing it with my friend, but it wasn't very strong.
I used to play with a level, or rather a power level, of about 10.
I used to play with a little bit less powerful ones.
I'm 20 years old now, and there are parts of me that are 20 years old,
But I also like to mess around with the other members,
I like to play around with the members a little bit, so I have a part of a 15 year old,
I'm not 15, but I'm in the first year of junior high school, so I think I have parts of a 13-year-old.
I have liked melon bread since I was quite young, but the moment I put it in my mouth, it became my favorite because of its softness and gentle taste.
How was the inside of the melon bread?
I think there are many melon breads that are crispy on the outside and soft on the inside, but the outside is soft and fluffy, and the inside is also soft and fluffy.
I would like to produce a melon bread that is fluffy on the outside and fluffy on the inside, something like "simple is the best".
I'm currently working on a project in which my specialty is mimicry that doesn't resemble anyone else.
Recently, I've been doing...
What was it again?
From Crayon Shin-chan.
Crayon Shin-chan.
O and then you get do remi faca solasi do and then you get Yoshiko Shinohara.
That's what I've been doing recently.
I'll try it. I'll try the line from Crayon Shin-chan, "OOI ORA NOHARA SHIN NUSUKE DA ZO.
I'm going to take the "O" out of "OOI ORA NOHARA SHIN NUSUKE DA ZO". OOI ORA NOHARA SHIN NUSUKE DA ZO
Doremifasorashido shinohara yoshiko desu!
I did that.
Oh, the monomaniac I want to learn is the one that has increased recently.
I'm trying to learn how to imitate a store clerk.
But I'm not ready to start with that yet.
I'm still stuck on Shinnosuke Nohara and Ryoko Shinohara.
I'd like to add more and more from here.
The reason I wanted to be Sumijiro Kamado from "Oni no Kensetsu no Kane" is because Sumijiro has a very kind heart and a really gentle personality, but he also has true strength, so I wanted to be someone like him.
I'm working on the current edition of "Wanokuni" and the otama-chan, what was his name again?
I want to be friends with all kinds of animals by eating their ears.
Ha-ha-ha-ha... Let's see...
Ironware.
Ironware is good for something.
I think that even in this day and age, people still use ironware a lot, and iron is used a lot in the early days.
I chose ironware because I think there are a lot of people who use iron in the early days. Interesting question.
I don't usually cook with Mario.
But I did cook that egg omelet before.
I made that omelette on Cookpad Live once, so I'm practicing omelette now.
I think I'm a blur person, and I like blurring things out.
The first CD I bought in my life was an album called "Album Tree" by The End of the World.
The first live concert I ever went to was also by The End of the World.
It was a big concert at a big venue, Inisser Stadium.
The End of the World
I applied for the concert of Sakagawa-san 3 times and all of them were unsuccessful, but when I was in the 2nd grade of junior high school
When I was in the second year of junior high school, he had a concert at Saitama Super Arena.
I applied for that concert, and to my surprise, I was in the sixth row from the front.
I was wearing a merchandise item of Mr. Social Story.
I was wearing Social Story merchandise, and it was projected on the monitor.
I have such memories.
Rather than setting a good example, my parents always taught me to be polite with my words, so I try to pay attention to it on a daily basis.
I have been very stiff since I was in junior high school, so...
Even on days when I want to go to sleep, I try to do 5 minutes of relaxation on the bed before going to bed.
My favorite cosmetics are brown, and lately I like brown makeup, so I use brown eyeshadow,
I use brown for eyeshadow, but I also use black mascara, and I mix a little pink and red for lips.
My makeup is not that beautiful, but once or twice a week I use a treatment in the bath that does not wash off.
When I look at my phone, I tend to curl my back a little bit and sometimes I walk in a strange way, so I try to be conscious of that in my daily life.
I used to leave my favorite food at school lunches when I was in elementary school, but recently I try to eat it first.
What do you buy at convenience stores?
Recently, I have been buying things at convenience stores,
I started an insta-story called "Reju's Melon Pan Tour," so I buy melon pan and salmon onigiri (rice balls).
What is the Melon Pan Tour?
The charm of Saitama Prefecture is that it is rich in nature, the air is clean and the greenery is delicious.
There are many shopping malls in Saitama, so I think you can have fun wherever you go.
My favorite Kansai dialect is "seyanaa.
I often end words with "I don't know," so it's "I don't know.
What games are you good at?
I have loved games since I was a child,
I'm good at all kinds of games, but recently I've been hooked on that notebook-type game,
I've recently been into those "no-touch" games.
One of these games is
Let's see...
What do you think has become more expensive? What do you think has become more expensive?I have answered many of your questions, so thank you for taking the time to look at this.
undefined